{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Base 10 refers to which number system?", "opta": "binary coded decimal", "optb": "decimal", "optc": "octal", "optd": "hexadecimal", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Convert the decimal number 151.75 to binary.", "opta": "10000111.11", "optb": "11010011.01", "optc": "00111100.00", "optd": "10010111.11", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Convert the binary number 1011010 to hexadecimal.", "opta": "5B", "optb": "5F", "optc": "5A", "optd": "5C", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The number of bits used to store a BCD digit is:", "opta": "8", "optb": "4", "optc": "1", "optd": "2", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Sample-and-hold circuits in ADCs are designed to:", "opta": "sample and hold the output of the binary counter during the conversion process", "optb": "stabilize the ADCs threshold voltage during the conversion process", "optc": "stabilize the input analog signal during the conversion process", "optd": "sample and hold the ADC staircase waveform during the conversion process", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The weight of the LSB as a binary number is:", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the difference between binary coding and binary coded decimal?", "opta": "Binary coding is pure binary.", "optb": "BCD is pure binary.", "optc": "Binary coding has a decimal format.", "optd": "BCD has no decimal format.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Convert the binary number 1001.0010 to decimal.", "opta": "125", "optb": "12.5", "optc": "90.125", "optd": "9.125", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Convert 110010012 (binary) to decimal.", "opta": "201", "optb": "2001", "optc": "20", "optd": "210", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the decimal value of the hexadecimal number 777?", "opta": "191", "optb": "1911", "optc": "19", "optd": "19111", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the resultant binary of the decimal problem 49 + 1 = ?", "opta": "01010101", "optb": "00110101", "optc": "00110010", "optd": "00110001", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "3428 is the decimal value for which of the following binary coded decimal (BCD) groupings?", "opta": "11010001001000", "optb": "11010000101000", "optc": "011010010000010", "optd": "110100001101010", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the result when a decimal 5238 is converted to base 16?", "opta": "327.375", "optb": "12166", "optc": "1388", "optd": "1476", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}